superservice.com 2015-06-27

# Superservice™ - Privacy Policy

## Infomedia Ltd Privacy Policy

  1. ### Introduction

This Privacy Policy is Infomedia Ltd's official policy relating to the collection and use of information from you. It applies to all information collected by Infomedia Ltd and /or its related bodies corporate (Infomedia). This policy explains how and why Infomedia collects your personal information, how it is used, and what controls you have over our use of it.

Infomedia is committed to complying with applicable laws governing the collection and use of personal information and to protecting and safeguarding your privacy when you deal with us.

  2. ### Purpose of collection

Infomedia collects information in order to:

    1. obtain important feedback about our products and services;
    2. deliver you websites with improved efficiency and functionality; and
    3. carry on its business and to provide its products and services to the various stakeholders such as customers, stockholders and the general public.

Without these details Infomedia would not be able to carry on its business and provide its services to you. Infomedia will only collect such personal information if it is necessary for one or more of our functions or services.

  3. ### Types of information collected by Infomedia

Infomedia collects a range of information in the ordinary course of its business activities, including personal and non-personal information. For example, we may collect information relating to your use of Infomedia’s products, services or websites.

  4. ### How Infomedia collects information

Infomedia gathers information in two ways:

    1. indirectly via the use of technology, for instance, via the placement of 'browser cookies; or other analytical tools on computers and devices used by you; and

    2. directly, for instance where:
      1. you buy or obtain a subscription to our software or services;

      2. you contact us (for instance; to obtain support or make an inquiry in respect of our products);

      3. you submit your email address for inclusion in our database;

      4. you browse any of Infomedia’s active websites or domains;

      5. you are a registered stock holder of Infomedia.

At or before the time we collect information, we will take reasonable steps to inform you about such collection, and draw your attention to this Privacy Policy and the [Cookie Policy](http://www.superservice.com/en/cookie-policy).
  5. ### How Information is used

You acknowledge and agree that Infomedia may use or disclose information for the primary purpose for which it is collected, including but not limited to, provision of services and administration related thereto, fulfilment of orders placed by you, notification about changes to our services, and general record-keeping during or after your use of our products and/or services. We may also use such information for a purpose related to the primary purpose of collection and where it a reasonable ordinary person would expect that we would use the information in such a way.

You acknowledge and consent that by providing your information to us that:

    1. we may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes: to order, supply and/or deliver goods to you, register and handle product warranties, communicate with you, to better understand our customer’s needs or to comply with our legal obligations;

    2. for these purposes, your personal information may be shared between Infomedia Ltd and its related bodies corporate, and may be disclosed on a confidential basis to our third party contractors, agents or to our suppliers;

    3. you represent to us that where you provide personal information to us about another person, you are authorised to provide that information to us, and that you will inform that person who we are, how we use and disclose their information, and that they can gain access to that information;

    4. we may include your personal information in a database compiled by us for use in direct marketing by us.

  6. ### Disclosure of information

Your information will only disclosed to parties outside our business in the circumstances set out in this policy or as otherwise notified to you at the time of collection of the information. Infomedia reserves the right to disclose your information where:

    1. we reasonably suspect that there is a threat to your safety or the public's health or safety; or

    2. we reasonably suspect that unlawful activity has been, is being or may be engaged in, and the use or disclosure is a necessary part of our investigation or in reporting the matter to the relevant authorities;

      1. where such use or disclosure is required under or authorised by law (for example, to comply with a subpoena, a warrant or other order of a court or legal process); and/or

      2. where we reasonably believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary for prevention, investigation, prosecution and punishment of crimes or wrongdoings or the preparation for, or conduct of, proceedings before any court or tribunal or the implementation of the orders of a court or tribunal by or on behalf of an enforcement body.

  7. ### Third party sources

Our website or other materials may contain links to websites owned and operated by third parties. Those third parties may collect personal information about you. Once you navigate away from Infomedia's webpage(s), this Privacy Policy no longer applies, and Infomedia disclaims any responsibility for the privacy practices of such third parties, or the content they provide. Further, Infomedia disclaims responsibility for information which is collected by a third party, not affiliated with Infomedia, and subsequently provided to Infomedia with or without your consent. You should always protect your privacy by reviewing the privacy policies of each third party with whom you interact.

  8. ### Security and Storage

The security of all information held by Infomedia is treated with great importance. Security measures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under our control. Information is held on secure servers in controlled facilities. Information stored within our computer systems can only be accessed by those entrusted with authority and computer network password sanctions.

The information we collect from you may be transferred to a foreign country and/or a third party for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, but only if such transfer is permitted by law, and the transfer is effected in accordance with such law.

Despite our efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 per cent secure. Consequently, Infomedia cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to it or from its websites, nor its online products or services. Users transmit all information at their own risk. Upon receipt of your transmission we make every effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for keeping your passwords and/or account information secret. You should be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

  9. ### Access to and Correction of Personal Information

Infomedia is committed to maintaining accurate, relevant and appropriate information about our customers, client and other stakeholders.

You may request access to your information through our Privacy Officer using the following contact details:

Privacy Officer  
357-373 Warringah Road  
Locked Bag 5009  
Frenchs Forest NSW 2086  
Australia  
Telephone: +61 (0)2 9454 1500  
Fax: +61 (0)2 9454 1799  
Email: [privacy@superservice.com](mailto:privacy@superservice.com)

Infomedia will consider your request in accordance with applicable privacy laws in place. Infomedia will provide you with access to a copy of the information it holds about you, and will permit you to update or change that information, unless:

    1. you cannot satisfy Infomedia that you are entitled to access the information; or

    2. Infomedia is entitled to refuse or withhold such access.

If you are refused access, we will provide reasons for such refusal upon your request. Please note that, for security reasons, Infomedia will not disclose sensitive security details under any circumstances, including such things as usernames, passwords or credit card information.

  10. ### Complaints

If you have a complaint about our Privacy Policy or the collection, use or safe disposal or destruction of your personal information, your complaint should be directed to us via email at: [privacy@superservice.com](mailto:privacy@superservice.com)

We will investigate your complaint and attempt to resolve any breach that might have occurred in relation to the collection, use or destruction of personal information held by us about you.

If you are not satisfied with the outcome of this procedure then you may request that an independent person investigate your complaint.

  11. ### Changes to Privacy Policy

If Infomedia decides to change its Privacy Policy, it will post changes on this Privacy Policy page so that users are always aware of what information is collected, how it is used and the way in which information may be disclosed. As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments.

  12. ### Contacts

If you require further information regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following email address: [privacy@superservice.com](mailto:privacy@superservice.com)

  13. ### Acceptance

You acknowledge and agree that your use of Infomedia's websites or products constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.
